export const AdditionQuestion = {
  question1: {
      question: "2 + 2 = ?",
      options: [3, 4, 5, 6],
      answer: 4
  },
  question2: {
      question: "5 + 1 = ?",
      options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 6
  },
  question3: {
      question: "8 + 3 = ?",
      options: [9, 10, 11, 12],
      answer: 11
  },
  question4: {
      question: "4 + 6 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question5: {
      question: "12 + 2 = ?",
      options: [10, 14, 12, 13],
      answer: 14
  },
  question6: {
      question: "7 + 5 = ?",
      options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
      answer: 12
  },
  question7: {
      question: "15 + 4 = ?",
      options: [18, 19, 20, 21],
      answer: 19
  },
  question8: {
      question: "6 + 9 = ?",
      options: [14, 15, 16, 17],
      answer: 15
  },
  question9: {
      question: "3 + 3 = ?",
      options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
      answer: 6
  },
  question10: {
      question: "10 + 5 = ?",
      options: [14, 15, 16, 17],
      answer: 15
  },
  question11: {
      question: "9 + 8 = ?",
      options: [16, 17, 18, 19],
      answer: 17
  },
  question12: {
      question: "11 + 3 = ?",
      options: [13, 14, 15, 16],
      answer: 14
  },
  question13: {
      question: "5 + 5 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question14: {
      question: "14 + 1 = ?",
      options: [15, 16, 17, 18],
      answer: 15
  },
  question15: {
      question: "20 + 10 = ?",
      options: [28, 30, 32, 34],
      answer: 30
  },
  question16: {
      question: "3+7=?",
      options: [9, 10, 11, 12],
      answer: 10
  },
  question17: {
      question: "13 + 2 = ?",
      options: [14, 15, 16, 17],
      answer: 15
  },
  question18: {
      question: "8 + 8 = ?",
      options: [14, 15, 16, 17],
      answer: 16
  },
  question19: {
      question: "16 + 4 = ?",
      options: [19, 20, 21, 22],
      answer: 20
  },
  question20: {
      question: "4 + 9 = ?",
      options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
      answer: 13
  },
  question21: {
      question: "7 + 8 = ?",
      options: [14, 15, 16, 17],
      answer: 15
  },
  question22: {
      question: "12 + 12 = ?",
      options: [22, 23, 24, 25],
      answer: 24
  },
  question23: {
      question: "5 + 6 = ?",
      options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
      answer: 11
  },
  question24: {
      question: "1 + 9 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question25: {
      question: "3 + 10 = ?",
      options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
      answer: 13
  },
  question26: {
      question: "6 + 6 = ?",
      options: [11, 12, 13, 14],
      answer: 12
  },
  question27: {
      question: "2 + 3 = ?",
      options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 5
  },
  question28: {
      question: "10 + 10 = ?",
      options: [19, 20, 21, 22],
      answer: 20
  },
  question29: {
      question: "9 + 4 = ?",
      options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
      answer: 13
  },
  question30: {
      question: "6 + 5 = ?",
      options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
      answer: 11
  },
  question31: {
      question: "1 + 1 = ?",
      options: [1, 2, 3, 4],
      answer: 2
  },
  question32: {
      question: "15 + 5 = ?",
      options: [18, 19, 20, 21],
      answer: 20
  },
  question33: {
      question: "7 + 4 = ?",
      options: [9, 10, 11, 12],
      answer: 11
  },
  question34: {
      question: "2 + 8 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question35: {
      question: "11 + 9 = ?",
      options: [18, 19, 20, 21],
      answer: 20
  },
  question36: {
      question: "9 + 6 = ?",
      options: [14, 15, 16, 17],
      answer: 15
  },
  question37: {
      question: "20 + 5 = ?",
      options: [24, 25, 26, 27],
      answer: 25
  },
  question38: {
      question: "4 + 5 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 9
  },
  question39: {
      question: "14 + 5 = ?",
      options: [18, 19, 20, 21],
      answer: 19
  },
  question40: {
      question: "6 + 10 = ?",
      options: [15, 16, 17, 18],
      answer: 16
  },
  question41: {
      question: "8 + 5 = ?",
      options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
      answer: 13
  },
  question42: {
      question: "12 + 9 = ?",
      options: [19, 20, 21, 22],
      answer: 21
  },
  question43: {
      question: "3 + 4 = ?",
      options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
      answer: 7
  },
  question44: {
      question: "5 + 15 = ?",
      options: [20, 21, 22, 23],
      answer: 20
  },
  question45: {
      question: "18 + 1 = ?",
      options: [19, 20, 21, 22],
      answer: 19
  },
  question46: {
      question: "7 + 6 = ?",
      options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
      answer: 13
  },
  question47: {
      question: "2 + 12 = ?",
      options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
      answer: 14
  },
  question48: {
      question: "6 + 2 = ?",
      options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
      answer: 8
  },
  question49: {
      question: "5 + 20 = ?",
      options: [24, 25, 26, 27],
      answer: 25
  },
  question50: {
      question: "4 + 7 = ?",
      options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
      answer: 11
  }
};

